[Music]
as a small or medium-sized business you
know that great product descriptions
boost sales by making products stand out
from the crowd but being creative on
demand is challenging especially when
writing product descriptions for dozens
or even hundreds of similar products no
one knows this better than Stan the
product manager at Nano Leaf Nano Leaf
is a pioneer of innovative smart home
lighting solutions it's an exciting time
for the team as they're about to launch
a new product line but authoring
engaging product subscriptions for their
online store takes time and creativity
co-pilot in Microsoft Dynamics 365
business Central helps successfully
launch new products with AI powered
experiences right from where you manage
your inventory Stan wants to register
their new product the Nano Leaf Skylight
and starts by uploading a picture
business Central analyzes the image and
suggests a category to minimize data
entry after quickly customizing
attributes and entering price and stock
levels Stan is ready to start copyright
writing so he can sell online with just
a click co-pilot uses natural language
technology to craft an engaging
description tailored to this product and
enriched with key data from the record
getting started with copyrighting has
never been easier hm let's see if we can
improve this further Stan can select
precisely which of the product
attributes are most relevant to describe
the Skylight and also choose a format of
generated text for consistency across
the product line pretty good Nano Leaf
is all about Innovation and with a few
more customizations Stan can match their
brand identity and tailor this to the
target audience with a more upbeat tone
of voice and look at that a creative
catchphrase followed by an informative
description that presents all the
facts after a quick review and a few
edits of his own Stan's text is ready
for Prime Time Nano Leaf uses business
Central's first party connector to
Shopify a leading e-commerce platform
which means that Stan is just seconds
away from publishing the Skylight to
their web shop and here it is ready for
you and I to purchase not only does
business Central accelerate time to
Market but having a great product
description that is engaging and
informative also improves conversion
rates so stop typing and start selling
with co-pilot in Dynamics 365 business
Central